We brought along the guys
that got beat up by him yesterday.
They'll tell you what happened,
and I think it'll make you reconsider his punishment.
You guys...
Come on. Hurry and cough it up, fellas.
W-well, Nishiwaki gathered up
a whole group of us yesterday.
He told us to lay the pressure on this
cocky freshman punk and get him to join our clique.
Yo. Why the hell are you in here playing basketball?
Don't you know that the Kuzu High basketball team
is just a bunch of trash?
I'm Nishiwaki, a senior here.
Nice to meetcha.
You're a freshman, right Natsume?
I'm gonna give you two options.
Agree to be one of my followers now,
or we beat the shit out of you until you do.
Not interested.
Get lost, dumbass.
Don't play stupid with me.
I told you to pick one, dammit.
I don't need your bullshit!
Do you get it now? Huh?
After that, he totally snapped and we got flattened.
Along with Nishiwaki and the rest.
Where to go? The land, sea or sky?
Ahiru no Sora
I wanna invite you to come along
The pages of our story have started to turn
If you lose your nerve then recycle it
And let it push you past hesitation
Give and go! With the flow
Instincts that are buried deep will always rear their head again
People can't just hide the dreams they once dreamed of
Even if these wings can't fly
We want to spread them wide and embrace the sky
Becoming the people who we want to be
You never know, the impossible could be possible tomorrow
So let's keep up the struggle
Happy go ducky!
So if the other guys started the whole fight,
Kite, His Ball, and the Team's Pain
that means it was self-defense! Right, teach?
Natsume being expelled was based on the fact
that students were injured as a result of his actions.
Even if it was in self-defense,
not all violent actions can be overlooked.
Are you saying he should've just sat there and taken it?!
Would you really do the same thing
in that situation, teach?!
Some pain in life must be borne with. Remember that.
Seriously?
This is why I hate dealing with authority.
We always get the short end of the damn stick.
You guys are free to go now.
Hold up.
Tell that punk Nishiwaki when you get back...
...that if he pulls this shit again,
then I'm gonna smash his face in personally.
What's your deal?
I never asked for or wanted any of your help.
Keep your nose out of this.
Look, I didn't come here trying to help you.
I just wanted to wipe the slate clean.
What?
Your ball... I'm sorry that I kicked it.
It's special to you, yeah?
The hell does that mean?
Quit making all this shit up.
What was all that about, Yasuhara?
Well, when we first met him, I picked up his ball
and kicked it without thinking.
And his fight with Nishiwaki's group
was triggered by the same thing.
Plus, when he accidentally hurt that girl,
it was only because he was so absorbed in basketball.
It didn't take me long to figure it out.
He's not a punk, just a dumbass
that loves playing basketball.
AH! I JUST REMEMBERED!
He promised to play basketball with us
if I managed to take the ball from him earlier!
It's special to you, yeah?
Hey, Kenji!
What's this? You playin' basketball again?
Hey! You!
Y-you talking to me?
Yeah, help me out!
If you got any spare paper, I could really use it.
Oh God, this dude is taking a shit...
Boy, you really saved my ass!
I called my little brother,
but it was already getting crusty down there!
You, uh, can just keep them.
It was a free pack of tissues, anyway.
Oh yeah? I really appreciate it, man.
By the way, that ball you have caught my eye earlier.
Are you basketball player?
I'm not so sure. I used to be, but maybe not anymore.
The school I just entered is kind of a dump.
There's not really a basketball team to speak of.
Plus, I just got expelled anyway.
I don't think I'll be playing much anymore.
I've got... a lot of regrets.
If you feel that way, then don't be a quitter
and just keep playing.
Momoharu!
Did you get a job as a toilet paper salesman or what?
You're the one who told me
to go and buy some, dammit!
You stupid shithead!
This guy is his... little brother?
"Kite" was your name, yeah?
Have you already decided to quit going to school?
That's none of your business.
I know our basketball team is pretty shitty.
All the skilled players hoping to join
always leave after taking a look at us.
But you know, there was just one guy who didn't.
How could you ever understand how I feel?
Because I was in a similar spot until recently.
Though, I don't know jack shit
about your personal problems.
But you gave up before even starting,
so doesn't that make you the loser?
Payphone
Okay! I'm waiting!
That's right... I am the loser.
Come on, teach! Cut the guy some slack!
I've heard enough from you.
Natsume's punishment is final. Just give it up.
That's why I'm here! I'm asking you
to please do something about it!
I've never met someone this hard to get through to.
Expelled students
need love, too
Please and thank you!
I'm beggin' you, Teach!
I find this hard to understand.
You and Natsume aren't even
on very good terms, are you?
Why go so far to cover for him?
I will admit that I don't really like the guy.
He's way too violent.
And his haircut makes him look like melon bread.
But...
I absolutely adore his basketball skills.
That's why...
Quit being a creep, dummy.
I've been looking for you, Mr. Satsuki.
Please, Teach. I want you to reverse
the decision to expel me.
What did you say?
Don't be absurd.
It's too late to change your punishment.
I don't expect it for free.
I'll make this school famous.
And as our advisor, you'll get to reap plenty of benefits.
What?
I'll take the Kuzu High basketball team...
all the way to the inter-high nationals.
Huh?
I thought you didn't want to be associated
with the basketball team.
What caused you to change your mind?
I guess I spent too much time around these idiots
and caught a case of the stupid.
I know I'm making a selfish request.
But I can't just turn tail and give up on everything now.
Please! Just give me one more chance!
You're being ridiculous.
And it's pointless to even bring this up
with me in the first place.
Because I have no authority in your case.
You need to accept the facts and gi-
Very well, then allow me to decide.
The Kuzu High team going to the inter-high nationals?
That's quite the promising prospect, if you ask me.
Who's that?
Mr. Principal!
So without further ado,
I'll be introducing the newest member of the team.
Natsume Kenj-
I'm Kite.
I look forward to playing with you.
Everything worked out, but only because
the Principal made a special exception in your case.
But do not forget that the conditions
on which the team can play remain the same.
None of this means that I've got any personal faith in you.
I get it.
I'm done. No more fights.
All right! Time for practice.
Your dribbling is still amazing
no matter how many times I see it.
How the hell do you hold the ball
to move it around so freely like that?
Nah, you don't hold it. You stick to it.
You said it yourself, remember?
It was almost as if the ball
was glued to your hand or something.
You can't just force the ball down,
you also have to lead it as it comes back up.
Of course, the ball won't actually stick to you
even if you're pulling it along.
The important thing is simply to maintain that image of it.
Cool. I think I get it.
When you get the hang of it, switch to your left hand.
And once you can do that,
then you use both hands. Two balls at once.
Mom.
Both hands?! That's gotta be impossible.
There are just so many amazing people in the world!
It's possible. Just watch this.
He made me realize that I've barely even
scratched the surface of the world of basketball!
Holy shit! You're amazing, dude.
Kanagawa School of Medical Science
Secondary Hospital
I was a little worried that we might get disbanded.
But now our team has an awesome lineup of members!
The cherry blossoms...
have already wilted away this year.
Well, April went by pretty quickly.
Oh, I can smell rain!
It doesn't seem like a storm is coming to me.
It will. Really soon.
Rain, huh? I hate when it rains.
I always end up slipping on the court.
But we can't even use the court today,
which means practice is outside.
That makes me hate the rain even more.
Although, it's not like our team
has even had proper training to begin with.
Which means days like this would be the prefect chance
to spend time building muscle instead.
And Mr. Satsuki doesn't really know anything
about basketball, anyway.
What we need now is someone who can figure out
a training schedule for us to keep...
Today I'm pulling out all the stops to make sure
you get the beating that you deserve.
Brace yourself.
Now get up, dammit!
What's the deal? You're not putting up
much of a fight this time.
And here I went out of my way to gather up
all these extra guys.
At least let us have a little fun-
My ball...
Don't touch... my ball...
Don't fuck with me, punk!
Y'know, I hear the basketball team
has gotten serious about playing lately.
Apparently, they got permission
on the condition that they don't cause any trouble.
Huh? Is that what's holding this little idiot back?
Well that sounds all sorts of fun.
If we get this guy to snap,
then the basketball team is finished.
And they've all been getting
on my nerves for a while now.
Especially those damn twins.
Come on, do it.
I'll let you take a totally free swing at me.
So just let the basketball team rot and die, okay?
No skin off our bones, Kite. Let him have it.
I'll even help if you want.
Y-Yasuhara, you little bitch!
We can avoid being disbanded if we just get rid
of the evidence after we beat the snot out of you turds!
That's right.
We can sweep it all under the rug after the fact.
But first, I wanna know which of you jerks
sent this ball raining down on me!
Uh... why don't you just go home and watch TV
with an afternoon snack or somethin'. Okay?
Why should I do that?! I can hold my own!
I'll take 'em to the cleaners!
I'll piledrive whoever threw this ball right into the dirt!
I don't need any help.
Just shut up and watch.
I don't even need to use my hands
to deal with losers like you.
Come on, do your worst.
You cheeky punk! I'll make you regret that!
Stupid freshman like you don't get to talk back!
Eat shit and die!
Hold on, Kite!
Stay out of it.
He's doing exactly what Satsuki told us we'd have to.
For real.
Some pain in life must be borne with. Remember that.
Right now, he's bearing all the pain
so that the basketball team can survive.
Kite...
That dumbass!
And it's our responsibility...
...to bear the pain of having
to watch him get beat up like this!
What are you boys doing?!
Shit, it's Satsuki!
Run for it!
Hold it! Stop right there!
Is fighting all those boys know how to do?!
For God's sake.
That goes for all of you, too!
As if you didn't cause enough trouble
with everything yesterday!
Listen up. The basketball team will now be-
Except we didn't cause any problems.
At least not this time.
Oh really?
Hey, Teach.
I thought maybe I could figure out...
the meaning of what you said yesterday, Mr. Satsuki.
But honestly...
...I don't think this whole "bear the pain"
thing is such a good fit for me.
Same here. I thought I was gonna have a heart attack.
You said it.
Yeah, screw that noise.
W-wait a moment!
What now?
I can't say no to eyes like those. Good grief.
From what I understand, the volleyball team
will be taking a break from practice today.
If you wish to use the court,
then you can have free reign of it.
Huh?
Sweet!
We can have a real practice session in the gym! Yahoo!
Yo.
Need a hand?
I can't believe this.
Your adorable new teammate was getting beat on,
and you all just stood there like rocks.
You were the one who told us to shut up and watch!
That was a figure of speech.
It finally stopped raining.
Okay, boys. Time to get pumped and start practicin'!
Whoa, Kite! What's up with your face?!
Don't tell me you got into another fight!
Wasn't a fight.
Not at all.
Probably.
But who can say for sure?
Does it really even matter?
So, hey.
I've been curious this whole time.
Why exactly do you go by "Kite"?
Isn't your name "Kenji Natsume"?
Cuz my dad was like a black kite,
up in the scaffolds at his job.
He "was"?
He's dead now.
He was working one day, when a sudden gust of wind
blew away the scaffolding he was on.
It was a headlong dive down 10 stories.
Dad...
Hey, Ken, we found this.
It was mixed in with all your dad's other stuff.
I want a legit basketball!
One of those fancy ones made from real leather!
Our family doesn't have that kind of money! Ya dummy!
It happened just three days before my birthday.
He was a cheapskate that drank a ton of booze,
but he was always a good father to me.
I never saw eye-to-eye with my new dad who
came along, and we just ended up fighting all the time.
I see now.
That's why he treasures that ball so much.
Yo. I'm glad you're getting along with us and all.
But I think there's one more
important thing you've still gotta do.
Go and apologize to Yoshino on the volleyball team.
You owe her that.
No worries.
We're real close friends now.
In body and soul.
Oh my gosh! Don't embarrass me, Kite!
I made you lunch today!
Oh, hey, Bro!
You know, this means war.
Huh?
Because Yoshino was number 8 on my list of girls
who I most wanted to start dating!
FACE MY DIVINE WRATH!
So fast!
I'm honestly surprised he's keeping up with my speed.
This shrimp is pretty good.
Okay, this is the last run!
Pass it over to me!
Hey, Tinytown. Wait a damn minute!
Have you lost your mind?
Who stops during a 2-man drill
to take a shot in the middle like that?
You don't have to worry about me!
I promise I won't miss any of my shots!
That's not the problem here.
Damn this little shrimp.
The level of accuracy his shots have is unbelievable...
Still, our practice sessions have only been
the same thing over and over.
Don't you have anything else that we can do, Captain?
You want some other drills?
Yo, Teach.
Quit staring and try actually coaching us for once.
You're our advisor, right?
That's true.
Then... how about you do some running?
Dammit, Momoharu. You and your big fat mouth.
Um, Momoharu?
I think we really need someone to help research
and plan a training schedule for us.
You're right. I'll think about it.
Okay, that's enough for today.
He must be trying to kill us, making us run 500 laps...
Oh, I nearly forgot.
This really doesn't pertain to any of you,
but the match schedule for the first semester is out.
Here's a copy of it for reference.
Crap, do the inter-high prelims
really start at the end of May?
We barely have a month left to practice, then!
Wow! There's also a tournament
just for the Kanto region!
That would be fun, I hope we can participate!
We're too late to have any hope of entering that.
The second round of games starts tomorrow.
Gah, you're right...
That sucks.
Oh!
Then let's go watch it! Together!
No way. That's too much effort, man.
I wanna go! Let's go!
Jeez! I can't believe how late you guys are!
I said we would meet up at 10 this morning,
but you kept me waiting for 4 hours!
Now we'll be lucky to even catch
the last quarter of the final game of the day!
Don't sweat it.
Ugh... I should have just gone with Kite
when he left earlier.
Seeing the final game of this round is more than enough.
Just look, I did some research online yesterday.
This is today's matchup.
This must be some kind of fate.
ABSOLUTE VICTORY
Defense! Defense! Defense! Defense...!
A steal...
Dammit!
Eirin
Shinmaruko
Blocking! #4 on Defense!
Maru High is losing... by 9 points even...
Whoa! According to this,
their opponents right now are a seeded team.
Charged timeout! Shinmaruko!
They were ranked in the top 8
of last year's Kanto region tournament!
We thought Maru High was tough as nails,
but even they're getting trashed out there.
Do you guys really think we can compete
in matches like these?
MA-RU-KO! MA-RU-KO! MA-RU-KO...!
Hang in there, Maruko!
You can do it!
This game...
...they still have a chance to turn it around.
Huh?
They ain't dead yet.
Listen up, Choji! I want you to stick to their #10 like glue!
Got it!
Sawa! If you get the ball and have an open shot,
always go for the three!
Even if you miss, I will DEFINITELY get the rebound!
Just leave everything that happens
inside the paint to me!
It's Chiba!
He's as passionate as ever. Totally on fire.
They're facing a full court press!
The other team doesn't want
Maru High scoring any points!
Tokiwa!
He's quick.
Here he comes!
Cover him!
Holy crap! He dunked it!
I've never seen a dunk in a high school game before!
That #4 is so cool!
Nice, Chiba!
This isn't good, he looks totally wiped.
He didn't even need a dunk to score on that play.
Yeah, that dude really only has
to raise his hand to reach the basket.
It looks like he's just wasting precious stamina to me.
He knows what he's doing.
There's no denying that the other team
is slightly better than they are.
But that only matters if they were playing
on completely even terms.
What do you mean?
Take a look.
Just a few more points to take the lead!
MA-RU-KO! MA-RU-KO! MA-RU-KO...!
Don't give up!
Even if he pushed his stamina to its absolute limit,
that's a cheap price to pay
for turning the momentum in their favor.
In moments like these, it becomes very clear
which team the crowd favors.
And that is exactly when comebacks
are most likely to happen.
That #4 down there, he really knows
how to play the game of basketball.
There's no doubt his team is strong.
Shinmaruko
Eirin
The game is over!
Insane! A total unknown managed
to beat a seeded team!
H-hot damn...
Those were some really sick moves.
I wanna be able to dominate the court just like them!
Yo! You were watching?
It didn't matter how long you stared up at the sky
That was kind of an embarrassing game for us.
You always said that you would never be able to fly
If we're struggling this much against a team
that hardly made the top 8 in Kanto,
One night I cried wondering how long it would take
it doesn't really bode well for our future.
Until I could finally reach you with my hands
As you can see, Kanagawa has the most intense
block of competition in the entire country.
Eventually I got used to just running away
Are you guys ready to get in on this?
Until the day I realized that was a weakness
For the time being, we're going to get a head start
on you by claiming the throne of Kanto.
So let's start it all over, right now
If you waste too much time, we'll leave you in the dust.
We'll be right on your heels. Don't worry.
The things precious to us were always close at hand
If our school is also in the Kanagawa block,
that means we can't reach the prefectural
prelims without beating Maru High.
We are never completely alone at any time in our lives
What do you think, Chiaki?
I say the bigger the challenge, the greater the reward.
The truth is that you can fly, wherever you want
Damn straight.
Spreading your wings to go far higher than anyone else
You sure sent me to one hell of a place.
The more tears that you shed
I'm cursing you, Dad.
I swear... this might kill me.
Then the stronger you become
Let's use those wings to travel the world over
It really sucks to admit, but we can't even stand
on equal ground with Maru High as we are now.
And find a path to a future that no one knows about
I'm gonna need way more practice.
Always, always, always
I ain't quitting until my shots
start going in the damn basket!
Walking onwards, all of us together
I'd kill for some ice cream...
Faster, stronger...
We gotta keep getting better!
Uh, so where exactly are we right now?
Sorry. I put us on the wrong train.
What do we do now?!
ENOSHIMA BRIDGE
I don't have anymore money left!
Okay boys, we're running home.
Are you serious?!
Ahiru no Sora
Next Time: Manager
Next time: "Manager."